<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kbruch.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBruch</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBruch</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBruchxx</name>
  <summary>Exercise Fractions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Вправи з дробами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxExercise Fractionsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KBruch is a small program to practice calculating with fractions and percentages. Different exercises are provided for this purpose and you can use the learning mode to practice with fractions. The program checks the user's input and gives feedback.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBruch — це невеличка програма, яку призначено для вдосконалення навичок з обчислень з дробами і відсотками. З цією метою у ній використано різні вправи. Програма перевіряє введену користувачем інформацію і повідомляє про результат.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBruch is a small program to practice calculating with fractions and percentages. Different exercises are provided for this purpose and you can use the learning mode to practice with fractions. The program checks the user's input and gives feedback.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Arithmetic exercise - in this exercise you have to solve a given fraction task. You have to enter the numerator and the denominator. This is the main exercise.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вправа з арифметики — у цій вправі вам потрібно буде розв’язати завдання з дробів. Вам слід буде ввести чисельник і знаменник відповіді. Це головна вправа програми.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxArithmetic exercise - in this exercise you have to solve a given fraction task. You have to enter the numerator and the denominator. This is the main exercise.xx</li>
      <li>Comparison exercise - in this exercise you have to compare the size of 2 given fractions, using the symbols &gt;, &lt; or =.</li>
      <li>Conversion exercise - in this exercise you have to convert a given number into a fraction.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перетворення — у цій вправі вам слід буде перетворити задане число на дріб.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxConversion exercise - in this exercise you have to convert a given number into a fraction.xx</li>
      <li>Factorization exercise - in this exercise you have to factorize a given number into its prime factors.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Розкладання на множники — у цій вправі вам слід буде розкласти задане число на його елементарні множники.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFactorization exercise - in this exercise you have to factorize a given number into its prime factors.xx</li>
      <li>Percentage exercise - in this exercise you have to calculate percentages.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вправа з відсотками — у цій вправі вам потрібно буде виконати обчислення, пов’язані з відсотками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPercentage exercise - in this exercise you have to calculate percentages.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://edu.kde.org/kbruch/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbruch</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdeedu/kbruch/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kbruch.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kbruch</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
